https://www.baerwinery.com/WordPress/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Baer Winery respects your privacy. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you.
We do not sell your personal information. We will not share your personal data outside Baer Winery without your consent, except as required by law or to protect Baer Winery its customers, or the public, and then only with partners who share Baer Winery commitment to protecting your privacy and data.
Our site uses a third party service to match browser cookies to your mailing address. We then use another company to send special offers through the mail on our behalf. Our company never receives or stores any of this information and our third parties do not provide or sell this information to any other company or service.
To opt-out of receiving our direct mail, you may send us an email at custerservice@baerwinery.com, call us at 425-483-7060, or send a written request to 19501 144th Ave NE, F-100 Woodinville, WA 98072. We will honor those requests, but please understand that it may take 10 business days for such mailings to end.
At any time you may contact Baer Winery with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion.
We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Comment Name *
Email *
Website
